<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
	<MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
		<MASTER_PAD_VERSION>3.01</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
		<MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>PADGen 3.0.1.35 http://www.padgen.org</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>
		<MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used by shareware authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software products. To find out more go to http://www.asp-shareware.org/pad</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
	</MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
	<Company_Info>
		<Company_Name>KnowledgeInbox</Company_Name>
		<Address_1 />
		<Address_2 />
		<City_Town />
		<State_Province />
		<Zip_Postal_Code />
		<Country />
		<Company_WebSite_URL>http://www.knowledgeinbox.com</Company_WebSite_URL>
		<Contact_Info>
			<Author_First_Name>Tarun</Author_First_Name>
			<Author_Last_Name>Lalwani</Author_Last_Name>
			<Author_Email>tarunlalwani@gmail.com</Author_Email>
			<Contact_First_Name>Tarun</Contact_First_Name>
			<Contact_Last_Name>Lalwani</Contact_Last_Name>
			<Contact_Email>tarunlalwani@gmail.com</Contact_Email>
		</Contact_Info>
		<Support_Info>
			<Sales_Email>tarunlalwani@gmail.com</Sales_Email>
			<Support_Email>tarunlalwani@gmail.com</Support_Email>
			<General_Email>tarunlalwani@gmail.com</General_Email>
			<Sales_Phone>Not Available</Sales_Phone>
			<Support_Phone>Not Available</Support_Phone>
			<General_Phone>Not Available</General_Phone>
			<Fax_Phone>Not Available</Fax_Phone>
		</Support_Info>
	</Company_Info>
	<Program_Info>
		<Program_Name>Screen Capture API</Program_Name>
		<Program_Version>1.0.0</Program_Version>
		<Program_Release_Month>03</Program_Release_Month>
		<Program_Release_Day>26</Program_Release_Day>
		<Program_Release_Year>2008</Program_Release_Year>
		<Program_Cost_Dollars />
		<Program_Cost_Other_Code />
		<Program_Cost_Other />
		<Program_Type>Freeware</Program_Type>
		<Program_Release_Status>New Release</Program_Release_Status>
		<Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
		<Program_OS_Support>Windows2000,WinXP,Windows2003,Windows Vista Starter,Windows Vista Home Basic,Windows Vista Home Premium,Windows Vista Business,Windows Vista Enterprise,Windows Vista Ultimate</Program_OS_Support>
		<Program_Language>English</Program_Language>
		<Program_Change_Info />
		<Program_Specific_Category>Graphics</Program_Specific_Category>
		<Program_Category_Class>Graphic Apps::Screen Capture</Program_Category_Class>
		<Program_System_Requirements />
		<File_Info>
			<File_Size_Bytes>252928</File_Size_Bytes>
			<File_Size_K>247</File_Size_K>
			<File_Size_MB>0.24</File_Size_MB>
		</File_Info>
		<Expire_Info>
			<Has_Expire_Info>N</Has_Expire_Info>
			<Expire_Count />
			<Expire_Based_On>Days</Expire_Based_On>
			<Expire_Other_Info />
			<Expire_Month />
			<Expire_Day />
			<Expire_Year />
		</Expire_Info>
	</Program_Info>
	<Program_Descriptions>
		<English>
			<Keywords>Screen Capture, Scrolling, Complete web page, complete</Keywords>
			<Char_Desc_45>KnowledgeInbox Screen Capture API </Char_Desc_45>
			<Char_Desc_80>KnowledgeInbox Screen Capture API is a COM based library</Char_Desc_80>
			<Char_Desc_250>KnowledgeInbox Screen Capture API is a COM based library. The library provides you with various methods for capturing, combining and comparing screenshots</Char_Desc_250>
			<Char_Desc_450>KnowledgeInbox Screen Capture API is a COM based library. The library provides you with various methods for capturing, combining and comparing screenshots. Features
·     Capture desktop screen
·      Capture active window
·      Capture a region on screen
·      Capture a window using window handle
·      Capture a region of window using window handle
·      Convert image from one format to another format
·      Capturing complete IE page</Char_Desc_450>
			<Char_Desc_2000>KnowledgeInbox Screen Capture API is a COM based library. The library provides you with various methods for capturing, combining and comparing screenshots.


Features

·      Capture desktop screen
·      Capture active window
·      Capture a region on screen
·      Capture a window using window handle
·      Capture a region of window using window handle
·      Convert image from one format to another format
·      Get Internet Explorer object from window handle
·      Capture complete web pages in Internet explorer using vertical and horizontal screen captures.
·      Compare two images and get difference between them
·      Combine different images
·      Complete documentation provided
·      Compatible with all COM supporting scripting languages
·      Many sample VBScript provided for various methods</Char_Desc_2000>
		</English>
	</Program_Descriptions>
	<Web_Info>
		<Application_URLs>
			<Application_Info_URL>http://www.knowledgeinbox.com/documents/screencapture.html</Application_Info_URL>
			<Application_Order_URL>http://www.knowledgeinbox.com/documents/screencapture.html</Application_Order_URL>
			<Application_Screenshot_URL>http://www.knowledgeinbox.com/documents/screencapture.html</Application_Screenshot_URL>
			<Application_Icon_URL />
			<Application_XML_File_URL />
		</Application_URLs>
		<Download_URLs>
			<Primary_Download_URL>http://www.knowledgeinbox.com/documents/screencapture.html</Primary_Download_URL>
			<Secondary_Download_URL />
			<Additional_Download_URL_1 />
			<Additional_Download_URL_2 />
		</Download_URLs>
	</Web_Info>
	<Permissions>
		<Distribution_Permissions />
		<EULA>Please read the following terms and conditions carefully before using this SOFTWARE
PRODUCT. Your use, distribution or installation of this copy of "SCREENCAPTURE API" 
indicates your acceptance of this License.

SOFTWARE PRODUCT here means Software, image files, all accompanying files, data 
and materials received with your order of "SCREENCAPTURE API".

If you do not agree to any of the terms of this License, then do not install, 
distribute or use the SOFTWARE PRODUCT. 

This SOFTWARE PRODUCT is FREE for personal use only and may be installed and used by 
on only one computer. Its component parts may not be separated for use on more 
than one computer. For commercial use of the this SOFTWARE PRODUCT please contact author.

All components accompanying the software are copyrighted 
by KNOWLEDGEINBOX and may not be taken apart, modified, used or published with other 
software or means except with the SOFTWARE PRODUCT software and may not be 
distributed or copied in any manner.

This SOFTWARE PRODUCT, all accompanying files, data and materials, are distributed 
"AS IS" and with no warranties of any kind, whether express or implied. The user 
must assume all risk of using the program. This disclaimer of warranty constitutes 
an essential part of the agreement. 

Any liability of KNOWLEDGEINBOX will be limited exclusively to refund of purchase 
price. In addition, in no event shall KNOWLEDGEINBOX, or its principals, shareholders, 
officers, employees, affiliates, contractors, subsidiaries, or parent organizations,
be liable for any incidental, consequential, punitive or any other damages whatsoever 
relating to the use of SOFTWARE PRODUCT.

In addition, in no event does KNOWLEDGEINBOX authorize you to use this SOFTWARE PRODUCT 
in applications or systems where SOFTWARE PRODUCT 's failure to perform can reasonably 
be expected to result in a physical injury, or in loss of life. Any such use by you is 
entirely at your own risk, and you agree to hold KNOWLEDGEINBOX harmless from any claims 
or losses relating to such unauthorized use.

This Agreement constitutes the entire statement of the Agreement between the parties on 
the subject matter, and merges and supersedes all other or prior understandings, 
purchase orders, agreements and arrangements. 

KNOWLEDGEINBOX the owner of the copyright of this SOFTWARE PRODUCT, all of its derivatives,
title and accompanying materials are the exclusive property of KNOWLEDGEINBOX. All rights 
of any kind, which are not expressly granted in this License, are entirely and 
exclusively reserved to and by KNOWLEDGEINBOX. You may not rent, lease, transfer, modify, 
translate, reverse engineer, de-compile, disassemble or create derivative works based 
on this SOFTWARE PRODUCT. You may not make access to SOFTWARE PRODUCT available to others 
in connection with a service bureau, application service provider, or similar business, 
or use this SOFTWARE PRODUCT in a business to provide file compression, decompression, 
or conversion services to others. There are no third party beneficiaries of any promises, 
obligations or representations made by KNOWLEDGEINBOX herein.

You may not disclose to other persons the data or techniques relating to this SOFTWARE 
PRODUCT that you know or should know that it is a trade secret of the KNOWLEDGEINBOX in 
any manner that will cause damage to KNOWLEDGEINBOX.

This SOFTWARE PRODUCT and all services provided may be used for lawful purposes only. 
Transmission, storage, or presentation of any information, data or material in 
violation of any Country, State or City law is strictly prohibited. This includes, 
but is not limited to: copyrighted material, material we judge to be threatening or 
obscene, or material protected by trade secret and other statute. You agree to indemnify 
and hold KNOWLEDGEINBOX harmless from any claims resulting from the use of this SOFTWARE 
PRODUCT, which may damage any other party.

</EULA>
	</Permissions>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
